Welcome back to the Amanda Seals Show. It's Amanda Seals here and I am joined with comedian, actor, producer, writer, James Davis.
We're going to go to the back of the class. What was James Davis like in school?
In school, I was just, I was very chill, getting in where I fit in. And then in high school, I played golf.
So I was on the golf team and that wasn't like the...
In LA?
Yeah, yeah. In LA. Yeah. I was playing golf since I was 12.
Yeah, I was trying to, I was trying to be the next Tiger Woods. I was trying to go pro. So I was, I was focused.
Oh, it was like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Are there any black teachers that you remember that had an impact on you?
Oh, hands down. Now, see, that's the thing. That's why Pomona was dope.
Because like, I really loved so many of my teachers.
Phyllis Jackson, she was an ex-Black Panther teaching black, black art history.
Ooh.
Yeah. Sid LaMelle, black, he had a class on the black diaspora.
Like all my black teachers, Valerie Thomas, she was my English teacher, but she was teaching,
she was putting me up on, you know, bell hooks, Toni Morrison, all those people.
And like, when you learn all that, you can't, there's a certain comedy you can't do.
I feel like that's when you see a difference and it's not a bad or a good thing,
but the people who know move differently.
We are, we are, we are.